A Guide to the Charles F. Gillette, Papers, ca. 1880-1985 (bulk 1918-1969)
Library of Virginia
- Maps, 1883-1961.
  - MA- Boston, Plan for Subdivision of Property at Little Nahant Belonging to Sally M. Simmons- 1901 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 30 x 47 cm.
  - MA- Boston, Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Metropolitan Park Commission, Contour Map of a Portion of Mystic River Basin, Cradock Bridge to Lower Mystic Lake- 1904 (Box OS Roll)
    Drawn by: William T. Pierce, Engineer; Size: 109 x 140 cm.
  - MA- Cataumet, General Plan for Scraggy Neck Cataumet Mass.- 1926 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 7)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers - Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 46 x 63 cm.
  - MA- Hingham, General Plan for the Subdivision of Planter's Hill and World's End- 1890 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 7)
    Drawn by: F.L. Olmsted & Co. - Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 69 x 91 cm.
  - MA- Oysterville, General Plan for Oyster Harbor Oysterville, Mass.- 1925 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 7)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers - Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 64 x 53 cm.
  - MD- Baltimore, Map of the City of Baltimore and a Portion of Baltimore County, MD, Showing Existing and Proposed Park Lands- 1903 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 7)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 71 x 65 cm.
  - MD- Baltimore, Building Plan of the Johns Hopkins University Baltimore, MD- 1906 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 7)
    Drawn by: Warren H. Manning, Landscape designer, Boston; Size: 31 x 58 cm.
  - MD- Baltimore, Plat of Guilford- 1942 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 7)
    Drawn by: The Roland Park Company; Size: 58 x 48 cm.
  - MD- Gibson Island, General Plan for Development of Gibson Island, MD- 1922 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 7)
  - ME- Mt. Desert, Northeast Harbor Plan for Harbor Park in Conjunction With Proposed East Shore Road- 1928 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 8)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers - Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 28 x 41 cm.
  - ME- Orono, University of Maine General Plan for Campus Showing Proposed Buildings and Roads...- 1948 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 8)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers - Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 41 x 61 cm.
  - MI- Ann Arbor, Barton Hills, Ann Arbor, MI- 1923 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 8)
    Drawn by: Prepared for the Huron Farms Company, by Olmsted Brothers - Landscape Architects, Brookline Mass.; Size: 52 x 21 cm.
  - MI- Ann Arbor, Barton Hills, Plan for Suggested Development of Lots- 1923 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 8)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 36 x 74 cm.
  - MI- Detroit (?), Belle Isle Park Preliminary Plan- 1883 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 8)
    Drawn by: Fredk. Law Olmsted; Size: 48 x 100 cm.
  - MI- Detroit (?), Topographical Map of Belle Isle Park Showing Contours- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 8)
    Drawn by: Surveyed by Eugene Robinson; Size: 48 x 100 cm.
  - NC- Asheville, Topographical Map of Part of Biltmore- 1891 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 9)
    Drawn by: Unsigned; Size: 71 x 86 cm.
  - NC- Asheville, Topographical Map of Biltmore Estate, Buncombe County, NC- 1895 (Box OS Roll)
    Drawn by: Olmstead, Olmstead & Elliot, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass; Size: 111 x 76 cm.
  - NC- Asheville, Guide Map of Biltmore Estate- 1896 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 9)
    Drawn by: Prepared by Olmstead, Olmstead & Elliot, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass; Size: 31 x 46 cm.
  - NC- Asheville, Topographical Map of Biltmore Estate Buncombe County, NC, Property of Geo. W. Vanderbilt, Esq.- 1895 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 9)
    Drawn by: Olmstead, Olmstead & Elliot, Landscape Archt's, Brookline, Mass; Size: 108 x 76 cm.
  - NC- Chimney Rock, Lake Lure Chimney Rock Mountains, Inc.- 1926 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 9)
    Drawn by: E.S. Draper, Landscape Architect & Engineer - Charlotte, N.C. - Atlanta, Ga.; Size: 48 x 78 cm.
  - NC- Franklin, General Plan Cullasaja Heights Highlands, NC- 1926 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 9)
    Drawn by: E.S. Draper, Landscape Architect & Engineer - Charlotte, N.C. - Atlanta, Ga.; Size: 29 x 43 cm.
  - NC- Lenoir, General Plan for Development of Lake Shore Section Happy Valley Lake Estates- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 9)
    Drawn by: Lenoir Blowing Rock Development Company; Size: 28 x 48 cm.
  - NC- Moore Co., General Plan for the Village of Pinehurst- 1895 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 9)
    Drawn by: Olmstead, Olmstead & Elliot, Landscape Archts, Brookline, Mass; Size: 22 x 33 cm.
  - NC- Tyron, Plan of Arrangement of Blue Ridge Forest a 17000 Acre All-Year Mountain Resort In the Carolina Mountains [2 sheets]- 1925 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 9)
    Drawn by: E.S. Draper - Landscape Architect & Engineer, Charlotte, N.C. - Atlanta, Ga.; Size: 29 x 44 cm.
  - NC- Tyron, Blue Ridge Forest General Plan for A Restricted Mountain Residence Subdivision...- 1926 (Box OS Roll)
    Drawn by: E.S. Draper, Landscape Architect & Engineer - Charlotte, N.C. - Atlanta, Ga.; Size: 128 x 183 cm.
  - NC- Tyron, Blue Ridge Forest General Plan for A Restricted Mountain Residence Subdivision...- 1926 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 9)
    Drawn by: E.S. Draper, Landscape Architect & Engineer - Charlotte, N.C. - Atlanta, Ga.; Size: 46 x 63 cm.
  - NJ- Cape May County., General Plan for Subdivision of Ocean City Gardens North End - Ocean City- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 10)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 56 x 86 cm.
  - NJ- East Orange, General Plan for Watsessing Park East Orange, NJ- 1901 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 10)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects; Size: 12 x 28 cm.
  - NJ- Echo Lake, Preliminary Plan for Echo Lake Park- 1923 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 10)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 17 x 51 cm.
  - NJ- Elizabeth, Union County Park Commission Warinanco Park Preliminary Plan [2 copies]- 1923 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 10)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 30 x 34 cm.
  - NJ- Essex County., General Plan for Eagle Rock Reservation- 1901 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 10)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape architects; Size: 38 x 72 cm.
  - NJ- Newark, General Plan For Branch Brook Park [2 sheets]- 1901 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 10)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects; Size: 180 cm.
  - NY- Albany, View of East Side of New State Capitol at Albany, NY- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    Drawn by: Unsigned; Size: 61 x 64 cm.
  - NY- Buffalo, General Plan of Cazenovia Park- 1886 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    Drawn by: Olmstead, Olmstead & Elliot, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass; Size: 56 x 68 cm.
  - NY- Buffalo, General Plan of Delaware Park- 1899 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    Drawn by: Olmstead, Olmstead & Elliot, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass; Size: 51 x 102 cm.
  - NY- Fishers Island, Preliminary Plan for Property of Fishers Island Club- 1926 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 30 x 93 cm.
  - NY- Montauk, General Plan for Subdivision of Wompenanit- 1897 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    Drawn by: F.L. Olmsted & Co. - Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 66 x 79 cm.
  - NY- Montauk, Plan of Part of Wompenanit, Montauk, L.I.- 1897 (Box OS Roll)
    Drawn by: F. L. and J. C. Olmstead, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 114 x 98 cm.
  - NY- Montauk, Plan of Part of Hither Hills- 1904 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 68 x 122 cm.
  - NY- New York, Plan of Prospect Park Borough of Brooklyn New York City- 1901 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    Drawn by: Designed by Olmsted, Vaux & Co.; Size: 23 x 36 cm.
  - NY- New York, Map of Forest Hills Gardens Situated at Forest Hills Borough of Queens, City of New York [4 sheets]- 1911 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    Drawn by: C.B. Fancy, Civil Engineer; Size: 61 x 108 cm.
  - NY- Roslyn, Engineers Country Club General Plan Showing Proposed Subdivision- 1920 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 50 x 83 cm.
  - NY- Scarborough, Sleepy Hollow Country Club Property- 1917 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 47 x 50 cm.
  - NY- Southampton, Shinnecock Hills Southampton, L.I.- 1907 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers and Downing Vaux, Brookline, Mass. - New York, N.Y.; Size: 43 x 65 cm.
  - NY- West Point, General Plan for the Landscape Development of the United States Military Reservation West Point, New York- 1911 (Box OS Roll)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 100 x 102 cm.
  - NY- Yonkers, General Plan for the Subdivision Into Roads and Building Sites of the William Mitchell Estate Bryn Mawr- 1890 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    Drawn by: F.L. Olmsted & Co. - Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 48 x 74 cm.
  - PA- Philadelphia, General Plan of The Plaza, South Broad Street Boulevard and League Island Park... [2 copies]- 1915 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 12)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 86 x 44 cm.
  - RI- Nayatt, Rhode Island Country Club General Plan- 1912 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 12)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 30 x 39 cm.
  - RI- Newport, Preliminary Plan for Proposed Improvement at the Southern End of Newport Harbor [2 copies]- 1897 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 12)
    Drawn by: Olmstead, Olmstead & Elliot, Landscape Archt's, Brookline, Mass; Size: 34 x 89 cm.
  - SC- Charleston, General Plan for the Yeaman's Hall Club Near Charleston, SC- 1925 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 12)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 46 x 46 cm.
  - TN- Kingsport, Ridgefields Subdivision Preliminary Plan- 1947 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 12)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 55 x 71 cm.
  - TN- Swanee, The University of the South Swanee - Tenn. General Plan for Swanee Military Academy [2 sheets]- 1946 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 12)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 43 x 37 cm.
  - VA- Lexington and surrounding counties, Map of Lexington Presbytery by Rev. C.R. Lacy- 1914 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 13)
    Drawn by: Drawn April 1914 at Franklin, W.Va. by C.R. Lacy and L.C. Gordon; Size: 81 x 65 cm.
  - VA- Newport News, Perspective Map of Newport News, VA, County Seat of Warwick County- 1891 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 13)
    Drawn by: American Publishing Co. - Water & Ferry Sts. - Milwaukee, Wis. U.S.A.; Size: Irregular
  - VA- Norfolk, Map of the Norfolk & Portsmouth Belt Line R.R. and Connections- 1913 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 13)
    Drawn by: Office of Superintendent, Port Norfolk, Virginia; Size: 104 x 76 cm.
  - VA- Northern Neck, Map of the Tidal Waters of the Potomac River- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 13)
  - VA- Richmond, Plan of Colonial Place, Section B Compromising Blocks 14 to 28 Inclusive, Property of Abbey Realty Corporation- 1910 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 13)
    Drawn by: T. Crawford Redd & Bro., Surveyors & Engineers; Size: 43 x 30 cm.
  - VA- Richmond, Map Showing Territorial Growth of Richmond- 1923 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 13)
    Drawn by: Department of Public Works; Size: 44 x 60 cm.
  - VA- Richmond, Windsor Farms, A Residential Development on the James River at Richmond, Henrico County, VA- 1926 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 13)
    Drawn by: John Nolen- Town Planner; Philip W. Foster- Associate, Harvard Sq., Cambridge, Mass.; Size: 70 x 83 cm.
  - VA- Richmond, Monument Annex Richmond's Most Desirable West End Property [real estate sales flyer]- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 13)
    Drawn by: Blanton & Co., 1114 E. Main Street, Richmond, Va.; Size: 41 x 43 cm.
  - VA- Virginia Beach, The Cavalier Hotel & Vicinity... [Virginia Beach area map]- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 14)
    Drawn by: Unsigned; Size: 43 x 36 cm.
  - VA- Yorktown, A Plan of York Town and its environs for Capt. Robert Anderson (1848)- 1909 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 14)
    Drawn by: Traced by, Charles F. Gillette, Landscape Designer, Richmond, Virginia; Size: 46 x 61 cm.
  - VA- Yorktown, Sketch showing property [Yorktown plan showing proposed subdivision]- 1910 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 14)
    Drawn by: American Cement Engineering Co.; Size: 33 x 48 cm.
  - VA- Yorktown, Copy of a Map Sheet No. 1 Military Reconnaissance... [Civil War map of Yorktown area] [2 copies]- 1919 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 14)
    Drawn by: Traced May 1919 by, Charles F. Gillette, Landscape Designer, Richmond, Virginia; Size: 46 x 46 cm.
  - VA- Yorktown, Plat of a part of the original Town of Yorktown... [2 copies]- 1919 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 14)
    Drawn by: Unsigned; Size: 51 x 42 cm.
  - VA- Yorktown, Campaign Maps Army of the Potomac Map No. 1 Yorktown to Williamsburg- 1919 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 14)
    Drawn by: Traced May 1919 by, Charles F. Gillette, Landscape Designer, Richmond, Virginia; Size: 46 x 28 cm.
  - VA- Yorktown, 'Reconnaissance of Secession Works and Plan of Siege of Yorktown...- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 14)
    Drawn by: Traced by, Charles F. Gillette, Landscape Designer, Richmond, Virginia; Size: 48 x 48 cm.
  - VA- Yorktown, [Four Civil War maps of Yorktown area, 2 copies]- n.d. (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 14)
    Drawn by: Traced by, Charles F. Gillette, Landscape Designer, Richmond, Virginia; Size: 46 x 74 cm.
  - WA- Seattle, The Uplands Seattle [2 copies]- 1925 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 15)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Massachusetts; Size: 47 x 55 cm.
  - WI- Isle of Pines, 'La Siguanea Birds Eye View of the New Winter Resort - Isle of Pines - WI [2 copies]- 1910 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 15)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 51 x 64 cm.
  - WI- Isle of Pines, Plan for the Town of La Siguanea Fronting on the Shore of La Siguanea Bay Isle of Pines, WI- 1910 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 15)
    Drawn by: Olmsted Brothers, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass.; Size: 49 x 74 cm.
  - WI- Milwaukee, General Plan of West Park- 1895 (Box 1, Drawer 1, Folder 15)
    Drawn by: Olmstead, Olmstead & Elliot, Landscape Architects, Brookline, Mass; Size: 51 x 53 cm.
- Personal Papers, 1865-1985 (bulk 1912-1968).
  Series VI is housed in five (5) archival boxes on shelf and arranged alphabetically by folder title. Included are correspondence, family histories, journals, clippings, internment records, and writings. The majority of this series consists of the personal correspondence of Charles F. Gillette. Also included are personal letters from his wife, Mrs. Ellen C. Gillette, as well as materials related to Filmore Cogswell, Mrs. Gillette's father. A Gillette family history, materials related to Mr. and Mrs. Gillette's 50th anniversary celebration, and will and estate information are also in this series. Memorial reminiscences of Gillette's life and career and an article by Dr. George Longest are also organized in this series.
  - Art and Architecture Illustrations, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Belk, Blanton, Memoir of Charles F. Gillette, 1950 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Bookplate, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Butler, Carlisle C., 1942-1944 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Checkbook Stubs, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Clippings- Charles F. and Ellen C. Gillette, 1912-1969 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Clippings- Miscellaneous, 1911-1943 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Cogswell, Fillmore (Father of Ellen C. Gillette), 1899-1939 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1951 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - European Trip Journal, 1912 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Fiftieth Wedding Anniversary, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Gillette Family History, 1865-1967 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Gillette, Ellen C., Correspondence, 1912-1928 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Insurance, Correspondence, 1936-1951 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Insurance, Premium Receipts, 1934-1941 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Insurance, Premium Receipts, 1942-1951 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Internment, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Longest, George- "Charles Gillette: Father of the Virginia Garden," 1985 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Newsome, Stuart, 1941-1945 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Robertson, Archibald, Memoir of Charles F. Gillette, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Webb, Clinton, 1968-1970 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Will and Estate, 1967-1969 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - OVERSIZE (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Photographs, ca. 1880-1969 (bulk 1920-1960).
  Series VII is housed in five (5) archival boxes on shelf and arranged alphabetically by folder title. This series consists of a mix of personal and business-related photographs. Several folders contain images of Charles and Ellen Gillette in their youth and young adulthood. Also of note are images of the Cogswell family on camping trips in Colorado and Connecticut circa 1880s. Items such as Christmas cards, brochures for ornamental statuary, and clipping are in this series also. Not all photographs have been separated into this series. In some cases, photographs and negatives have remained with the client correspondence files (SERIES II).
  - Albermarle Paper Co. (Ethyl Corp.)- CCN 4 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2176; Photographs: 4
  - Battle, Hyman L.- CCN 35 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 609; Photographs: 2
  - Blow, George P. - "Deer Park" - La Salle, Ill. (Box 99, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 42; Notes: See also oversize photographs
  - Blow, George P.- CCN 170 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 56; Photographs: 15; Notes: See also oversize photographs
  - Brady, Mrs. Nicholas- CCN 1204 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 327, 380, 389, 390; Photographs: 6; Notes: See also oversize photographs
  - Brooke's Bank, Essex Co., VA (Box 99, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 6
  - Bryan, Jonathan- CCN 1106 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 19, 439, 698; Photographs: 2; Notes: See also oversize photograph
  - Crosley Corporation- CCN 1205 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 630; Photographs: 3
  - Davidson College- CCN 179 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 790; Photographs: 3; Notes: See also oversize photographs
  - Edgarton, N. Edward- CCN 218 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 372; Photographs: 1; Notes: See also oversize photographs
  - Furniture (Box 99, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 23
  - Gardens - Miscellaneous - 35mm Slides (Box 99, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 16
  - Gillette, Charles F. - 105 East Cary St.- CCN 985 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 446; Photographs: 68; Notes: See also oversize photographs
  - Gillette, Charles F. - 1214 Rothesay Circle - "Crestmere" (Box 99, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 4
  - Gillette, Charles F. - 2221 Grove Ave.- House- CCN 1165 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 189; Photographs: 16
  - Gillette, Charles F. - 2221 Grove Ave. - Garden- CCN 1165 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 189; Photographs: 52
  - Gillette, Charles F. - Christmas Cards, 1916-1921 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 7
  - Gillette, Charles F. - Gillette Family Photographs (Box 99, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 8
  - Gillette, Charles F. - Personal Photograph Album (Box 99, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 78
  - Gillette, Charles F. - Portraits (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Gillette, Ellen C. - Family Photographs (Box 100, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 31
  - Gillette, Ellen C. - Family Photographs - Camping (Box 100, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 19
  - Gillette, Ellen C. - Portraits (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 1; Notes: See also oversize photographs
  - Governor's Mansion- CCN 299 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2000; Photographs: 3
  - Hayes, John G.- CCN 339 1202 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 50, 940, 667, 458; Photographs: 2; Notes: See also oversize photographs
  - Hooker, Mrs. Elon Huntington- CCN 361 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 398, 682; Photographs: 2
  - Jeffress, Robert, 1934- CCN 1207 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 391; Photographs: 9; Notes: See also oversize photographs
  - Latham, Arthur- CCN 959 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2061; Photographs: 11
  - Love, Mrs. S.B. (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Manning, Warren H., 1937 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 1
  - Metalwork (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Morton, Mrs. David C.- CCN 957 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 411; Photographs:; Notes: See Williams, T. C.
  - Norton, E. Hope- CCN 569 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 889; Photographs: 31
  - Ortman, Randolph- CCN 1126 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 106; Photographs: 2; Notes: See also oversize photographs
  - Parrish, J. Scott- CCN 600 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 104, 179; Photographs: 5; Notes: See also oversize photographs
  - Postcards (Box 100, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 14
  - Reed, Leslie H.- CCN 680 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 74, 220; Photographs: 2
  - Rhoads, W. S.- CCN 1208 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 409; Photographs: 3
  - St. Giles Church- CCN 1111 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 626; Photographs: 7
  - St. Isaac Jogues Novitiate (Box 101, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 52; Notes: See also oversize photographs
  - Statuary (Box 101, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 33
  - Statuary (Box 101, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 41
  - Sundials (Box 101, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 13
  - U.S. Army Photographs - World War II (Box 101, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 5
  - Urns and Vases (Box 101, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: None; Photographs: 20
  - Vesper, F. W. A.- CCN 1206 (Box 101, Folder 7)